NADER NASR

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

■ nadernasr7@gmail.com • www.nadernasr.ca • (647) 510 - 9223 • Toronto, Ontario in linkedin.com/in/nnasr/ • NaderNasr

SUMMARY

Full stack Web Developer with a solid background in software development with 4+ year within the technology sector. I wanted to enhance my foundational background in JavaScript and be able to continue creating websites that are valuable to end customers. With this goal in mind, I recently completed my Full Stack Web Development Diploma. I enjoy creating applications that are one of a kind, useful and has great purpose for the daily lives of others.

SKILLS

FRONT-END: React, Axios, SASS, Webpack, HTML, Three.js, CSS, Svelte

BACKEND: Express, PostgreSQL, Node.Js, MongoDB, AWS

LANGUAGES: JavaScript, Ruby, Ruby on Rails

TESTING: Jest, Cypress VERSION CONTROL: GIT

UI/UX: Figma, StoryBook, Styled Components, Material UI, Bootstrap, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe After Effects, Adobe InDesign

EMPLOYMENT

OjaBox, Front-End Developer, Dubai, UAE

Jan. 2019 - Dec. 2019

Worked closely with client, product managers and designers to conceptualize new features with building the company website to create a new online platform that offers users the ability to create, share, purchase, and sell various 3D content and VR Assets for use within the augmented reality industry. Designed, developed and launched the company website including a content library and 3D rendering tool using Three.js

• Launched the OjaBox website using Reactjs, AWS, NodeJs, ThreeJs, Material UI

360VUZ, Technical Project Manager, Dubai, UAE

Aug. 2016 - Jan. 2018

Managed 2 remote mobile development teams in India and a web development team in Ukraine in creation of the 360VUZ mobile application that broadcasts live concerts and events to the subscriber using the Oculus Gear VR.

Administered the project budget, tracked expenses, monitored performance, and ensured milestones were met.

Collaborated with the client to establish technical direction, introduce functions, and gain consensus on changes.

Kev Achievements:

• Achieved the original launch deadline date by overcoming various technical issues without affecting performance and helped grow downloads from 50,000 in the first year to over 500,000 in the second year by optimizing the functionality

Rubicon Group Holding, Virtual Reality Unity3D Developer, Amman, Jordan

Aug. 2014 - July 2016

Developed applications and educational games for the Oculus Gear VR using Unity 5

Liaised with team members throughout the software development lifecycle to achieve established milestones Key Achievements:

• Created an interactive digital comic book for kids using Unity 5 that could be played on their mobile devices

EDUCATION

Lighthouse Labs

Diploma Full Stack Web Development

Jan. 2018 - Mar. 2018

Jan. 2022 - Apr. 2022

RBK (Amman, Jordan) Certificate Full Stack Web Development

Seneca College

Aug. 2011 - Aug. 2014 Advanced Diploma Interactive Media Design

PROJECTS

Mar. 2022 - Mar. 2022 ARt - Commerce

Stack - ReactJs, PostgreSQL, CommerceJs, NodeJs, Axios, MaterialUI, Stripe, Model-viewer An E-commerce application that utilizes augmented reality for art, and wall decorations

Interview Schedular Feb. 2022 - Feb. 2022

ReactJs, Axios, Sass, Webpack, Express, PostgreSQL, NodeJs, Jest, Cypress, StoryBook, React test renderer React application that allows users to book and cancel interview in real time with an API server.

June 2018 - July 2018 Portal Mixed Reality

React Native, AWS, Bcrypt, Express, Mongoose, NGrok, React Native Router Flux, Express Augmented and Virtual Reality Educational App made with React Native and Viro react